Hello friends, my name is Ashwini Kumar.
As friends, you
already know me here.  Friends, I am
already selected in ICICI Bank here.  The
topic of today's video is going to be the
same, friends,
you must have already seen it in the title and thumbnail.
Brother, many people are facing problems here.
Many people have already
sent me messages.  And friends, by commenting,
he has also filled my comment box here.  They have only
one message that our result of
IDFC First Bank has not come yet.
Have we failed?  Or
those children who have already received the
message, have already received a notification on their mail,
friends,
you are going to get that update here in today's video.
Brother, many
people have already given the exam of
IDFC First Bank Emerging
Program here, as you already know
that I had already made a video on it
when this program was launched here.
So friends,
I made a video regarding this program.  Well,
I have already made a lot of videos here.
After watching that video, many people had applied
and they
also got the assessment test link and they had
applied and they had
also given their test.  So now friends are
waiting because their result is not coming out.
Their result is not being declared.
And brother, I too am going to have a new update
for you in today's video.
IDFC
is the first emerging bank whose
program is going to be held here.  For this, friends, there is going to be some
good news for you here.
Friends, here
in today's video I am going to give you
complete information step by step.  For this,
friends, you have to do only one thing.   You
must watch the video till the end.  If you like the video, please give it
a like.   If you are
new to the channel then friends, you
must subscribe to the channel.  Because
you keep getting such content here.  Without
wasting any time let's start the video.
Friends, in today's video we are talking
about IDFC First Bank,
friends, I had already
made a video on it here in which I had
told you.  Regarding its program, they have
launched a program here by
tying up with Manipal Academy,
friends, their first
program is going to be held here, the first batch is going to be there
and brother, many children had
shown their interest in it and
brother, many children had also applied for it
and brother, friends, many
children here have also conducted its exam or
not, so brother, friends,
next time the link was sent to them from
there, friends, they had
conducted the exam here, many people are
already selected here, that is,
their result has already come here,
friends, there is a YouTuber, some mail
etc. has been sent to him.  As I will
show you here on the screen also.  This male
brother, this male brother has gone to him.  Now
brother, he is saying in this mail that brother, the
result has reached me.  Brother, I have already been
selected.  So friends, nothing like this is going to happen.  Anyway, the
mail has already reached everyone.  To all those people who have
not received the mail yet.  So brother, please
wait a little.  It may be delayed by 1 day or 2 days.
But brother, it is 100 to 100% yours if
you have connected it properly here.  That
means, if
you have asked questions etc. in this, then brother,
you will get its result here 100 to 100%.
Rest of the brothers, I have also received
its result.  Like here
I will put the screenshot for you.
I have received a mail regarding this.  Dear
Ashwin Kumar, Greetings from your IDFC
Manipal Academy for BFSI.  We are placed to
inform you that growing session has been
scheduled to help you prepare for
upcoming interview with IDFC First
Bank and role as Relationship Manager.
So brother, it is clearly
written here that brother, you have been selected
but what will happen now, your
next round is going to happen, that is,
before the interview is going to happen here, friends, you are being given grooming training here from the Manipal Academy site, that is,
in that training you will be told
how you have to give the interview,
you have to speak in this manner here.  How do I
tell you about IDFC First Bank?
How do you tell about your program?  How to
interact with them.  Friends, in this way, there is going to be a
grooming session here.  Friends, this is Microsoft,
which is an application of Microsoft.
Friends, a meeting is going to be held here on this issue.
In the meeting, brother, you will be explained how the
interviews are
conducted.  How do you
give your answers here in the interview?  That
means, the brother who is going to be your final round
interview will be the
HR of your IDFC First Bank.  And friends, there will be
an HR from your Manipal who is going to
take your interview personally.  Online
friends, your interview is about to take place.  100
to 100% friends, if you
take this session here brother.  Well friends, there is nothing like that
here that
after taking this session your interview will be
cleared.  There is nothing like that friends.
Because brother friends are not going to interact with you here.  Whatever he
says, he will say it to himself.  I
will just explain it to you.  You can tell me the questions.  We will
not give you so much knowledge etc. here.  So
friends, what do you have to do here?   Brothers,
if you want to attend this session then
you can do it easily.
If brother, you have received the mail.
Friends, this mail that I have received,
two dates are written in it.
But brother, the one I received was
received on the 3rd.  And
friends, when I tried to open it here,
brother, it had expired.  That means I received
this mail after 1 day.  So brothers, all of you friends, till now
you are waiting for the result of this IDFC First Bank.  Especially the
friends who have taken help from me here,
they are waiting because their
declaration has not been done, so friends, please
wait for one to two days.  After waiting for one to two days,
you will receive an email.
Friends,
I guarantee this 100% that those friends whom I have
helped here, there is
no need to worry.  They are going to get 100
to 100% mail.
Friends, I have received this mail.
I have not attended its session etc. here
because brother, I do not need it.  By the way
brother, whenever its final round takes place here,
you will be informed before that.
Before that you will be informed that your
round is on that day.  Friends, what you have to do here is
that you have to
prepare well.  If friends, you
want to prepare for this,
not for this, not for IDFC, either friends, you
want to be for Axis or for HDFC
or for IDFC or friends, for
ICIC Bank, for any of these banks,
friends, you want to be prepared for the interview here, you
want to prepare for the interview, then friends,
for that, we have launched a special training
here.  Like
you will easily find its banner here on the side.
Or friends,
what do you want to do?  Below you will find a link to the
WhatsApp group.  Go and join the
WhatsApp group friends.  Please send me a
personal message.
Friends, the training details will be shared with you here.
There
you just have to type yes here.  As soon as you
type yes, you have to type after training yes.
Like brother, if you do that then the
details will be shared with your friends here.
Rest of the friends, if anyone has any questions regarding IDFC
First Bank, then
please comment here in the comment box.
Your friends, the reply here will be 100
to 100% yours.
Friends, I have already told you about IDFC First Bank
that the result has not been declared yet.
Those who have received the mail, well and good.
Those who have not received the mail, please
wait a little.  I have
come to my place one day later after waiting for one day.  So brother, it will come to you 100%.  If he does
n't come today, brother, he will come to
you by tonight.  But you have to wait.   It is
not that if you do not have to wait here then
brother you will have to wait.
You have no option.  Those
friends who are already selected and those brothers who have
already been rejected will
not receive any mail etc.  By the way, he will receive
a mail saying it has been rejected.  So friends, just
wait, your result will be out in one to two days.
Otherwise brother, if you
want to prepare for the interview then
you can connect with us.  100 to
100% friends, your interview will be
cleared here.  Rest friends, in today's
video I have told you about IDFC First Bank.
I hope
you liked this information in today's video.  If you like the
video then please like it.
Friends, if you have
not yet subscribed to this channel, then brother,
go quickly and subscribe to this channel.
See you in the next video.
Ok.  Take care.  Bye